jaguars.com 2018-04-14

# 1. Information Collection

                                            Effective Date: November 6, 2017
Jacksonville Jaguars, LLC and Jacksonville Jaguars Foundation, Inc. (collectively, “Jaguars,” “we,” “our,” “us”) respect
your privacy and value your trust and confidence. This privacy policy (the "Privacy Policy") applies to our websites
(www.jaguars.com,            www.jaguarscubclub.com,             www.jaguarsblack.com,          www.jaguarsarcade.com,
www.myjaguarsaccount.com, www.myjags365.com, www.myjaguarsblack.com, www.everbankfield.com), our
mobile application (Jacksonville Jaguars app) and authorized online services that link to or post this Privacy Policy
(collectively, the "Services"), and explains how we collect, use, and disclose information through the Services. By
using the Services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Please note that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information that is collected or obtained through sites or
services that do not link to this Privacy Policy (including the “Shop” page on our website) or information collected by
the NFL Entities. “NFL Entities” means collectively, NFL Ventures, L.P., NFL Ventures, Inc., NFL Productions LLC, NFL
Enterprises LLC, NFL Properties LLC, NFL International LLC, all of the NFL member clubs (excluding Jaguars), any
successor or future entity that is, directly or indirectly, jointly owned and/or controlled by all or substantially all of
the NFL member clubs, or owns assets that produce revenues that are required to be shared with other NFL member
clubs under the NFL Constitution (including any such entity controlled by the NFL member clubs and the Jaguars
collectively) and each and all of their respective affiliates, subsidiaries, successors and assigns.
We have received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed
for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The
TRUSTe       certification   only     covers      information     collected     on    our    websites www.jaguars.com,
www.jaguarscubclub.com, www.jaguarsarcade.com and our “Jacksonville Jaguars” mobile application (the “Mobile
App”). If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please
contact TRUSTe at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Please click on any of the following links to navigate to its respective section.
          1. Information Collection                       7. Children’s Privacy
          2. Use of Information                           8. Changes To This Privacy Policy
          3. Sharing of Information                       9. Access and Choice
          4. Social Media Services                        10. Your California Privacy Rights
          5. Links To Other Web Sites                     11. International Users
          6. Security                                     12. Contact Us
1.   INFORMATION COLLECTION
You generally are not required to provide information about yourself when you visit the Services. However, we may
ask you for some or all of the following types of information when you register with our Services, sign up for contests,
promotions or sweepstakes, use a send-to-a-friend feature, participate in surveys, access various content or
features, submit comments or content, or directly contact us with questions or feedback:
         Contact information, such as name, e-mail address, postal address, or telephone number;
         Unique identifiers, such as a user name, password or Jaguars ID;
                                                           1 of 7

         Device information, such as device carrier, operating system type and version, or Android ID;
         Demographic information, such as gender or age;
         Financial information, such as credit card or other payment information;
         Geolocation information;
         Communications preferences;
         Search queries;
         Comments and other information posted in our interactive online forums;
         Correspondence and other information that you send to us;
         Third party information, such as a friend’s name and email address; and
         Additional information as otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
When you provide us with personal information about your contacts, we will only use such information about third
parties for the specific reason for which it is provided.
We also may collect certain information automatically when you visit the Services, including:
         Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, which is the number automatically assigned to your computer
          whenever you access the Internet and that can sometimes be used to derive your general geographic area;
          we also use IP addresses for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to our
          advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of
          our sites. We may combine this information with other personally identifiable information, such as name,
          telephone number, email, age, or address, which will be used in accordance with Section 2 of this Privacy
          Policy;
         Other unique identifiers, including mobile device identification numbers;
         Your browser type and operating system;
         Sites you visited before and after visiting the Services;
         Pages you view and links you click on within the Services;
         Information collected through cookies, web beacons, local shared objects, and other technologies;
         Information about your interactions with e-mail messages, such as the links clicked on and whether the
          messages were received, opened, or forwarded; and
         Standard Server Log Information, such as IP address, browser type, Internet service provider (“ISP”),
          referring/exit pages, operating system and date/time stamp.
Click-stream data is information collected by our computers when you request web pages from the website. Click-
stream data may include such information as the page served, the time, the source of the request, the type of
browser making the request, the preceding page view and other such non-personal information. When analyzed,
this data helps us analyze how visitors arrive at the website, what type of content is most popular, what type of
visitors in the aggregate are interested in particular kinds of content and advertising, and the like.
If you wish to sign up for the Jaguars Arcade, you will be asked to provide certain information to our social media
content service provider (currently, Umbel) in order to do so. The type of information that is collected is name,
email address, date of birth, and password. This information is then shared back with us and will be used in
accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
Email Communications: When you open emails from us, we may receive a confirmation noting you opened the
email, if your computer supports such capabilities. We also may keep track of what emails we send you and what
emails, if any, you are receiving from our subsidiaries and affiliates. Additionally, we keep a record of what
communications you have opted to receive or not to receive.
We may use cookies, pixel tags, Local Shared Objects such as HTML 5 (sometimes referred to as “Flash Cookies”),
and similar technologies to automatically collect this information. Cookies are small bits of code that are stored by
your computer’s web browser and that may automatically identify your browser to the Services whenever your
computer is used to visit the Services. Pixel tags are very small images or small pieces of data embedded in images,
also known as "web beacons" or "clear GIFs,” that can recognize cookies, the time and date a page is viewed, a
description of the page where the pixel tag is placed, and similar information from your computer or device. Flash
                                                           2 of 7

Cookies are similar to standard cookies except that they can be larger and are downloaded to a computer or mobile
device by the Adobe Flash media player. Please note that you may need to take additional steps beyond changing
your browser settings to refuse or disable Local Shared Objects and similar technologies. For example, Local Shared
Objects can be controlled through the instructions on Adobe’s Setting Manager page. By using the Services, you
consent to our use of cookies and similar technologies. You can decide if and how your computer will accept a cookie
by configuring your preferences or options in your browser. However, if you choose to reject cookies and similar
technologies, you may not be able to use certain online products, services or features on the Services.
As true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may
include IP addresses, browser type, ISP, referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream
data. We do not link this automatically collected information to information we collect about you other than IP
address. We collect this information to help us improve our website and to deliver a more personalized service. At
times, we also use the information for purposes of system administration and to report aggregate information to
our advertisers and sponsors, for example regarding the frequency with which our guests visit various parts of our
sites. Click-stream data is described above in the fourth paragraph of this section called “Information Collection”.
We use mobile analytics software to allow us to better understand the functionality of our Mobile App on your
mobile device. This software may record information such as how often you use the application, the events that
occur within the application, aggregated use and performance data, and from where the application was
downloaded. We do not link the information we store within the analytics software to any personal information
you submit within the Mobile App.
User Data Supplementation
We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly-available databases or third parties
from whom we have purchased data, and combine this data with information we already have about you. This helps
us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and provide products and services that may
be of interest to you. If you provide us personal information about others, or if others give us your information, we
will only use that information for the specific reason for which it was provided to us.
Examples of the types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or purchased from third
parties and combined with information we already have about you, may include:
          Address information about you from third party sources, such as the U.S. Postal Service, to verify your
           address so we can properly send you products and to prevent fraud; or
          Purchased marketing data about our customers from third parties that is combined with information we
           already have about you, to create more tailored advertising and products.
2.   USE OF INFORMATION
We may use information that we collect through the Services for a variety of purposes, including to:
          Provide you with the products, promotions, services, newsletters, and information and respond to
           correspondence that we receive from you;
          Contact you via email and otherwise about your account and about products, services, contests, and events
           that we think might be of interest to you;
          Send you promotional material or special offers on our behalf or on behalf of our marketing partners and/or
           their respective affiliates and subsidiaries and other third parties;
          Send you push notifications from our Mobile App to alert you of new features within the Mobile App or
           update you regarding the Services;
          Administer contests, competitions, sweepstakes, surveys or voting;
          Locate an exact place you may be looking for near the stadium or to facilitate the purchase of tickets,
           concessions or other items;
                                                           3 of 7

        Maintain or administer the Services, perform business analyses, or for other internal purposes to improve
         the quality of our business, the Services, and other products and services we offer;
        Publish stories, comments, photos, and other information posted in our interactive online features;
        Send your friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site; we store this information for the sole
         purpose of sending a one-time email advertisement and tracking the success of our referral program. Your
         friend may (a) contact us at 904-633-6000; (b) opt-out of receiving emails via the one-click opt out contained
         in the email advertisement; or (c) add link to preferences page to request that we remove this information
         from our database;
        Customize and personalize your use of the Services; and
        As otherwise described to you at the point of collection or pursuant to your consent.
3.   SHARING OF INFORMATION
We are committed to maintaining your trust, and we want you to understand when and with whom we may share
the information we collect.
        Service Providers: We may share your information with service providers that perform certain functions or
         services on our behalf (such as to host the Services, fulfill orders, provide products and services, manage
         databases, perform analyses, provide location maps, process credit card payments, host our websites or
         any of our subdomains (including but not limited to shop.jaguars.com), provide customer service, or send
         communications for us). These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as
         necessary to provide these services to us.
        Subsidiaries and Affiliates: We may share your information with Jaguars subsidiaries and affiliates for the
         business purposes described herein. In addition, we may share your information with all members of the
         NFL family, including, without limitation, the NFL Entities. Such information may be used by the NFL Entities
         for internal business purposes and to learn more about Jacksonville Jaguars fans in the Jacksonville
         marketplace.
        Select Business Partners: With your permission, we may share your information with select business
         partners so that they can provide you with special offers, promotional materials, and other materials that
         may be of interest to you. For example, you may be presented with an opportunity to have certain
         information shared with our third party business partners when you enter a contest or sweepstakes or elect
         to receive marketing offers or other information. If you do not elect to have your information shared, it
         will not be shared with such third parties. We take measures to help ensure that our partners protect the
         confidentiality, integrity, and security of any information we share with them. However, we are not
         responsible for the privacy practices of our business partners, which may use your information for their
         own purposes.
        Third-Party Ad Serving and Audience and Traffic Measurement Services: We may use third-parties to
         display advertisements on the Services. These third parties may set their own cookies or similar web
         technologies to collect information about users’ online activities over time and across different websites.
         To manage your preferences you may opt out here http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/ or if located in the
         European Union, here http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/. Please note you will continue to receive generic
         ads.
        Business Transfer: If we sell all or part of our business, or make a sale or transfer of assets, or are otherwise
         involved in a merger or business transfer, or in the event of bankruptcy, a business reorganization, or similar
         event, we may transfer your information as part of such transaction.
        Administrative or Legal Process: We may disclose your information to third parties in order to protect the
         legal rights, safety, and security of our organization, our business affiliates, subsidiaries, business partners,
         and the users of our Services; enforce our Terms of Use; respond to and resolve claims or complaints;
         prevent fraud or for risk management purposes; and comply with or respond to law enforcement or legal
         process or a request for cooperation by a government or other entity, whether or not legally required.
                                                           4 of 7

          Interactive Features: We may share information that you post information to a user profile or a public area
           of the Services, such as a chat room, forum, blog, or other community tool with third parties. If you post to
           these interactive features, it will be publicly available and you may receive unsolicited messages from other
           parties. We cannot ensure that parties who have access to such information will respect your
           privacy. Please exercise caution when using these features.
          Other Parties With Your Express or Implied Consent: We may share information with third parties when
           you consent to such sharing. For example, if you win a contest, competition or sweepstakes, we may ask
           your permission to publicly post certain information on the Services identifying you as the winner.
          Aggregate Information: We may share aggregate information, such as demographic and usage statistics,
           with advertisers, sponsors or other organizations.
          Contests, Promotions or Sweepstakes: If you participate in a contest, promotion or sweepstakes on our
           site, we may ask your permission to allow us to publicly post some of your information on the website. Such
           information may include name and prize.
Technologies such as cookies, web beacons and similar technologies are used by the NFL Entities and their respective
affiliates, and by our marketing partners and affiliates to collect information. These technologies are used in
analyzing trends, administering the websites, tracking user’s movements around the websites and to gather
demographic information about the NFL’s user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these
technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.
4.    SOCIAL MEDIA SERVICES
We have worked with certain third-party social media providers to offer you their social networking services through
our Services. For example, you can use third-party social networking services, including but not limited to Snapchat,
Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Google+, Hi-Fi, Stre.am, and others to share information about your experience on
our Services with your friends and followers on those social networking services. These social networking services
may be able to collect information about you, including your activity on our Services. These third-party social
networking services also may notify your friends, both on our Services and on the social networking services
themselves, that you are a user of our Services or about your use of our Services, in accordance with applicable law
and their own privacy policies. If you choose to access or make use of third-party social networking services, we
may receive information about you that you have made available to those social networking services, including
information about your contacts on those social networking services.
You also may be able to link an account from a social networking service (e.g., Snapchat, Facebook, Twitter,
Instagram, Google+, Yahoo!) to an account on our Services. This may allow you to use your credentials from the
other site or service to sign in to certain features on our Services. If you link your account from a third-party site or
service, we may collect information from those third-party accounts, and any information that we collect will be
governed by this Privacy Policy.
Public Forums: The Services includes publicly accessible blogs or community forums. For specific information
regarding the terms of use for such blogs or forums, please review the Jaguars’ Terms of Use, available in the footer
section of www.jaguars.com. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read,
collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog or
community forum, contact us by phone at 904-633-6000. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your
personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.
5.    LINKS TO OTHER WEB SITES
The Services may contain links to other websites or online services that are operated and maintained by third parties,
such as Fanatics (shop.jaguars.com), and certain of our media partners and sponsors, and that are not under the
control of or maintained by us. Such links do not constitute an endorsement by us of those other websites, the
                                                             5 of 7

content displayed therein, or the persons or entities associated therewith. This Privacy Policy does not apply to that
third-party content. We encourage you to review the privacy policies of those third-party websites or services.
6.   SECURITY
We have adopted security procedures to help protect against loss, misuse, and unauthorized access to the
information you provide to us. For example, if we collect financial information, we will use encryption software to
help protect this information when it is in transit. Please note, however, that no data transmission or storage can be
guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your information and privacy, we cannot
guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to the Services and cannot be
responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your information.
7.   CHILDREN’S PRIVACY
The Services do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose personal information from children under the age of 13. If we
are made aware that we have collected on the Services personal information from a child under 13 years old in a
manner that is inconsistent with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), we will delete this
information as soon as possible.
8. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Services after any modification to the
Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the new terms. If we make any material changes we will notify you
by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on the Services prior to the
change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our
privacy practices.
9.   ACCESS/CHOICE/RETENTION
Upon request delivered to marketing@jaguars.com, we will provide you with information about whether we hold
any of your personal information.
You may choose to receive promotional emails, newsletters, push notifications, and similar communications from
us. You may opt out of receiving promotional emails or push notifications from us by clicking on the opt-out or
“unsubscribe” link included in the promotional e-mails you receive, or by turning them off at the device level. Please
note that opt-out requests may take some time to be effective. Your opt-out request will not apply to messages that
you request or that are not promotional in nature. For example, we may contact you concerning any purchases you
have made with us, even if you opt out of receiving unsolicited promotional email messages. To manage your
communications subscriptions, please visit http://fanservices.jaguars.com/updatemail.
If your information changes, or if you no longer desire to use the Services, you may request that we update or remove
certain information by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will
try to respond to your request within 30 days.
We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you Services. We will
retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our
agreements.
If you no longer wish to allow us to track your geolocation information or further receive push notifications in a
Mobile App, you may turn these off at the device level.
If you believe that one of your contacts has provided us with your personal information and you would like to request
that it be removed from our database, please contact us at marketing@jaguars.com.
                                                          6 of 7

10. YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our
disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request,
please contact us by phone at 904-633-6000 or write us at Jacksonville Jaguars, LLC, 1 EverBank Field Drive,
Jacksonville, FL 32202, Attention: Marketing.
In some cases, third parties may be able to collect information about a user’s online activities over time and across
different websites when the user uses our Services.
Some web browsers may transmit “do-not-track” signals to the websites with which the user
communicates. Because of differences in how web browsers incorporate and activate this feature, it is not always
clear whether users intend for these signals to be transmitted, or whether they even are aware of them. Because
there currently is no industry standard concerning what, if anything, websites should do when they receive such
signals, we currently do not take action in response to these signals. If and when a final standard is established and
accepted, we will reassess how to respond to these signals.
11. INTERNATIONAL USERS
Please note that the Services are directed towards users who reside in the United States. By using the Services, you
consent to the collection, storage, processing, and transfer of your information in and to the United States, or other
countries and territories, pursuant to the laws of the United States. While some of these countries may not offer
the same level of privacy protection as your own, we commit to uphold the privacy protections as explained in this
Policy.
12. CONTACT US
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the privacy practices of the Services, please contact us by
phone at 904-633-6000 or by postal mail at: Jacksonville Jaguars, LLC, 1 EverBank Field Drive, Jacksonville, FL 32202,
Attention: Legal. For questions regarding your account information, please contact marketing@jaguars.com.
                                                        7 of 7
